blablawriting.com 2016-10-06

# Privacy And Policy - Bla Bla Writing

BlaBlaWriting LLC (herein after referred to as “BlaBlaWriting”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the Bla-Bla-Writing.com website and governs data collection and usage. This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms and Conditions, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you. By using the Bla-Bla-Writing.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this policy.

COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Bla-Bla-Writing.com website collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, user name, address or telephone number when you sign up for our website and access it. Bla-Bla-Writing.com also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your Postal/Area codes and country.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Bla-Bla-Writing.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Bla-Bla-Writing.com to deliver personalized service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the Bla-Bla-Writing.com website.

Payment details 

In case of Customers, we may ask for your credit card detail, which is used for payment. These details are handled through our secure servers and will be securely stored. However, please remember that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data like credit card details through Bla-Bla-Writing.com links/public messages, this information may be collected and used by others. Bla-Bla-Writing.com does not read any of your private online communications and will not be responsible for its content and use by third parties.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Bla-Bla-Writing.com does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If Bla-Bla-Writing.com learns that personally identifiable information of persons below 13 years of age has been collected on the Website without verified parental consent, then Bla-Bla-Writing.com will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Bla-Bla-Writing.com collects and uses your personal information to operate the Bla-Bla-Writing.com website. We also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Bla-Bla-Writing.com and its affiliates. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Bla-Bla-Writing.com does not sell, rent or lease its registered User lists to third parties. We may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. When you subscribe to our mailing list, Bla-Bla-Writing.com may use it for email marketing, but protect the users’ information and make sure it is secure. All third parties whose services are used by BlaBlaWriting are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Bla-Bla-Writing.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Bla-Bla-Writing.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Bla-Bla-Writing.com keeps track of the websites and pages our Users visit within Bla-Bla-Writing.com, in order to determine what Bla-Bla-Writing.com services are the most popular. This data may be used to deliver customized content and advertising within Bla-Bla-Writing.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

DISCLOSING YOUR INFORMATION

Bla-Bla-Writing.com website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Bla-Bla-Writing.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Bla-Bla-Writing.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Bla-Bla-Writing.com, or the public.

THIRD PARTY LINKS

Bla-Bla-Writing.com may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. These third party sites have their own privacy policies. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of websites you choose to link to from Bla-Bla-Writing.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Bla-Bla-Writing.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on websites outside of the Bla-Bla-Writing.com.

USE OF COOKIES

Bla-Bla-Writing.com website may gather information about your general Internet use by using cookies. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Bla-Bla-Writing.com website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience.

Bla-Bla-Writing.com website may also gather information such as IP address, internal session ID, user’s domain, type of Internet browser, domain of Website. Such information will not identify you personally: it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save your time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Bla-Bla-Writing.com pages, or register with Bla-Bla-Writing.com site or services, a cookie helps Bla-Bla-Writing.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information. When you return to the same Bla-Bla-Writing.com website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Bla-Bla-Writing.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Bla-Bla-Writing.com services or websites you visit.

Third party links provided on our website may also use cookies, over which Bla-Bla-Writing.com has no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on their advertisement banners on our website or visit their sites.

SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Bla-Bla-Writing.com may transfer your personal information and submitted content that Bla-Bla-Writing.com collects from you to our main server for processing and storing. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Bla-Bla-Writing.com will take all reasonable steps to make sure that your data is treated securely without any loss, misuse or alteration of information and in agreement with this Privacy Policy. Bla-Bla-Writing.com secures the information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.

While you can terminate your account at any time, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or termination of your account. However, we will not sell, transfer, or use the information relating to the terminated account of an individual in any way.

By writing a testimonial you agree that BlaBlaWriting is allowed to use your testimonials linked to your account or not for marketing purposes. BlaBlaWriting is also allowed to place your testimonials on pages of Bla-Bla-Writing.com

You can always contact support team and ask to block / remove your testimonials if you feel that it may harm your educational profile.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore Bla-Bla-Writing.com cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY AND OPT-OUT

Bla-Bla-Writing.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. We may notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our web pages. However, Bla-Bla-Writing.com encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how Bla-Bla-Writing.com is protecting your information.

YOU MAY CHOOSE TO “OPT-OUT”/STOP RECEIVING OUR NEWSLETTER OR MARKETING EMAILS BY FOLLOWING THE UNSUBSCRIBE LINK INCLUDED IN THESE EMAILS OR BY SENDING AN E-MAIL TO support@bla-bla-writing.com.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Bla-Bla-Writing.com welcomes your suggestions and questions regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Bla-Bla-Writing.com has not adhered to this Policy, please contact Bla-Bla-Writing.com at support@bla-bla-writing.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
